## Kohji Noguchi BA (Hons)

Hidaka city, Musashidai 3-10-8 Saitama prefecture, Japan WhatsApp: +44 7511 800522
Email: kohji.noguchi0522@gmail.com
Portfolio / Linkedin

# **Objective**

Goal-focused Web content creator looking for a Japanese speaking Content Reviewer focusing on improving web contents including maintenance, updating Web sites, and managing CMS, eCommerce in general and creating web pages, improving user experience. I'm familiar with HTML, CSS, JSON and WordPress as my portfolio proves as above. I have 3 years of experience in total in the Web creating and eCommerce field in Japan and the UK. This also stands for the fact that I can smoothly fit into an international organisation and contribute to a team that has multi-cultures. As my below achievements show I experienced how to improve SEO from lower layers to top page to improve Google search. Now I'm taking an online Google UX design course to get a certificate and learn how to solve problems, improve customer experience, so I'm really motivated to improve services and attract customers with those knowledge and skills.

## **Employment history**

#### Apr 2022 - Sep 2022, Design, UI/UX & Marketing Manager at Gander Limited

- Designed & improved anti-food waste app UX design by Figma and adobe XD.
- Researched user behaviours at actual jobsite and suggested the best solution for retailers.
- Analysed more than 20 competitor's apps to research UX trends.
- Created mockups, decks for meeting by Figma and adobe XD.
- Created web banners instead of asking design agencies for saving 50% labour cost in total.
- Maintained, updated existing app and web site.
- Joined local events to increase app presence by sharing leaflets and face to face communication with instruction.
- Tested developing apps and reporting results to developers.
- Tested actual web site to double check whether it was based on design files.
- Liaised and managed with several design marketing agencies.
- Kept track of the number of downloaded app for market research.
- Assisted PR to cope with coverage (Channel 5) in order to expand app presence.
- Collaborated with freelancers to create stand banner design for an international conference.
- Arranging schedules for variety meetings including job interviews, clients and freelancers.
- Assisted expanding market in Japan and Asian area by negotiating with major Japanese media and companies.
- Customer service via phone and email.

### Jan 2022 - Mar 2022, Japanese Customer Service Agent at Gamesys Group

- Maintained customer retention rate 40% above the company average.
- Answered product and service questions and offered information on related products and services.
- Managed 50 customers KYC on daily basis averagely with 3 different brands simultaneously
- Maintained a customer account information database (incl. cancelling and updating customer accounts.)

#### Aug 2021 - Jan 2022, E-Commerce Assistant at NIVTAR DISTRIBUTION LIMITED

- Have achieved SEO rank up from page 6 (rank 70) to the top page (rank 6) by content editing of more than 100 web pages and contributed to increasing sales by 20 %.
- Have experience in operating 30 photo & video shootings with Ortery.
- Have experience in website blog containing more than 30 articles relocation accurately.
- Have experience in photo editing by photoshop (Cut, size arrangements, image composition).
- Have experience in creating web banners to improve brand presence.

#### Apr 2012 - Aug 2021, Several positions at various British and Japanese companies

- Web coder developed and maintained more than 20 websites.
- International salesmen contributed 70% sales revenue of small machines with 3 years of customer service experience including call and email.
- Import coordinator coping with more than 10 ocean/air shipping simultaneously.

#### Education

# **Skillset**

- •HTML(pug), CSS (sass/bootstrap), Javascript (jQuery), CMS (wordpress/drupal/shopify), gulp, Git.
- English(advanced/B2 IELTS 6.0), Japanese(native).
- •Design for digital interfaces.
- Teamwork and communication.
- Proactive and self-motivated.
- ·Hard-working, diligent, punctual.
- Eager to learn.
- High resilience and strong motivation to achieve goals

### **Tool**

• Sketch / Invision / Adobe Suite / Figma / Microsoft products.